I will be talking about respecting to
我将谈论尊重
Java 8 this has been a surprisingly
Java 8这真是令人惊讶
popular topic over the last year or so
过去一年左右的热门话题
because we've seen presentations about
因为我们看过关于
how about how Java 8 has introduced new
Java 8如何引入新的
features like lambdas and streams and so
诸如lambda和流等功能
forth and we've seen presentations about
第四，我们已经看到了有关
how to use them in new code but what's
如何在新代码中使用它们，但是
kind of more applicable to most of us as
更适合我们大多数人
day-to-day developers is how do we take
日常开发人员是我们的方式
an existing code base and perhaps move
现有的代码库，也许会搬家
it in the direction of Java 8 and
朝Java 8的方向发展
perhaps also understanding some of the
也许也了解一些
pros and cons of doing this and some of
这样做的利弊
the trade-offs so that's what this talk
权衡，这就是这个话题
is is aimed to answer but first before
旨在回答，但首先
we do that let's take a quick look at
我们这样做让我们快速看一下
why should we move to Java 8 well Java
为什么我们要向Java 8迁移呢？
is now nearly three years old so I'm
现在已经快三岁了，所以我
guessing probably a lot of people
猜大概很多人
already using Java 8 or considering it
已经在使用Java 8或正在考虑使用它
and probably one of the most compelling
可能是最引人注目的之一
reasons is the fact that Java 6 and 7
原因是Java 6和7
are end-of-life and no longer officially
寿命终止，不再正式
supported so it's a good idea to move to
支持，因此移至
Java 8 just for those reasons but there
Java 8正是出于这些原因，但是在那里
are some really compelling reasons to
是一些令人信服的理由
argue when you're trying to push your
当你试图推动自己的时候争论
case to management or to the support
管理层或支持者的情况
team or to ever inside your organization
团队或组织内部
cares about these things about why you
在乎这些事情，为什么你
should be adopting some of the job 8
应该采用一些工作8
features firstly Java 8 is generally
首先是Java 8的特性
faster than previous versions of Java
比以前的Java版本更快
you don't even have to do anything or
您甚至不需要做任何事情，或者
use any of the new features to get some
使用任何新功能来获得一些
of these speed improvements for example
这些速度改善中
some of the common data structures are
一些常见的数据结构是
faster there's some speed improvements
更快，速度有所提高
around concurrency and so forth and for
并发等等
more information about this click on
有关此点击的更多信息
that link because there's some links to
该链接，因为有一些链接
additional documentation about that of
有关以下内容的其他文档
course it's easy to paralyse that's the
当然很容易瘫痪
point about some of the stream
关于一些流
operations the fact that you can run
您可以运行的事实
stream operations in parallel without
流并行操作，无需
having to manage things like thread
必须管理诸如线程之类的东西
pools or executive services or so forth
池或执行服务等
it's just it can be done quite easily
只是很容易做到
for you you write fewer lines of code as
为您编写更少的代码行
a hardcore long term Java person maybe
一个铁杆长期的Java人
this wasn't the most compelling reason
这不是最引人注目的原因
for me but in actual fact once you get
对我来说，但实际上一旦你
used to using the Java 8 style you start
习惯于使用Java 8风格开始
to see that what you're writing is what
看看你在写什么
you want to achieve not how to do it and
你想实现不怎么做，
that's quite nice but takes away a lot
很好，但是可以带走很多东西
of the boilerplate and stuff that your
样板和东西
eyes were kind of ignoring and lets you
眼睛有点无视，让你
focus on what's really important in the
专注于真正重要的是
code and they've been
代码，他们一直
to do things like pass around lambda
做类似lambda传递的事情
expressions or use the streams API gives
表达式或使用API​​提供的流
you new solutions to problems and
您为问题提供了新的解决方案，
perhaps lets you solve things you
也许可以让您解决自己的问题
couldn't have solved before one of the
在其中之一无法解决之前
areas I think is under and publicized is
我认为正在宣传的领域是
that some of the Java 8 features let you
Java 8的某些功能可以让您
minimize errors we'll see some examples
最小化错误，我们将看到一些示例
of where we can minimize things like
我们可以最大限度地减少诸如
copy and paste errors using lambda
使用lambda复制和粘贴错误
expressions but there are other things
表达，但还有其他事情
like optional and other features that
如可选功能和其他功能
let you minimize the amount of errors
让您最小化错误数量
that accidentally creep into your code
意外地潜入您的代码
and also things like the streams API and
还有流API和
the added readability reduction of
增加了可读性
boilerplate can let you see much more
样板可以让您看到更多
easily where you've made a silly mistake
容易在您犯了一个愚蠢的错误的地方
so let's go straight on into the
所以我们直接进入
refactoring side of things but before we
重构事物的一面，但是在我们之前
do any sort of refactoring we really do
做我们真正做的任何形式的重构
need to have a safety check to make sure
需要进行安全检查以确保
that we're in the right place to do some
我们来对地方了
refactoring firstly it's really
首先重构是真的
important to have automated acceptance
具有自动接受能力很重要
tests if you're going to do any
测试您是否要执行任何操作
refactoring because although a lot of
重构是因为尽管很多
the research things I'm going to show
我要展示的研究内容
you the the idea is the functionality
你的想法是功能
will remain the same
将保持不变
you can't be sure that you haven't
您不能确定自己没有
accidentally changed some functionality
不小心更改了某些功能
if you don't have automated tests that
如果您没有自动测试
prove to you your code still does the
向您证明您的代码仍然可以
same thing it used to do performance
用来表现的东西
tests are important for the same sort of
测试对于同一种
thing and in fact we'll talk quite a lot
事情，实际上我们会谈论很多
about the performance of some of these
关于其中一些的性能
refactorings as we go through this talk
在本次演讲中进行重构
so you'll get an idea for perhaps how
所以您可能会想到
using Java 8 idioms impacts the
使用Java 8习惯用法会影响
performance of your code if performance
您的代码的性能，如果性能
is important to you it's important to
对您来说很重要
have tests to prove that you haven't
有测试来证明您没有
done something weird to impact the
做一些奇怪的事情来影响
performance and when I say involves
性能和我说的涉及
performance is important I don't
性能很重要，我不认为
necessarily just mean sort of nanosecond
一定只是意味着纳秒级
latency for high-frequency trading or
高频交易的等待时间或
whatever I sometimes mean things like
不管我有时候是什么意思
responsiveness to the user in less than
对用户的响应能力小于
half a second or something like how long
半秒或类似的时间
does it take an Android app to make a
是否需要Android应用来制作
call to the backend so these aren't
打电话给后端，所以这些不是
necessarily I'm not talking about high
一定我不是在说高
performance I'm talking about making
我正在谈论的表现
sure that you have performance tests for
确保您进行了性能测试
the things that really matter to you
对您真正重要的事情
performance wise before you do any sort
在进行任何形式的操作之前都要明智地执行
of refactoring you really need to decide
重构，您真的需要决定
as a team as an organization why you're
作为一个团队作为一个组织，为什么你
going to do this refactoring and there
要做这个重构，在那里
are a number of different reasons we've
我们有许多不同的原因
talked about things like performance and
谈到诸如性能和
readability removing boilerplate and
可读性删除样板和
removing errors you can also do respect
消除您也可以尊重的错误
for learning you might want to upskill
学习，您可能想升级
the team on a code base on a domain
团队基于域的代码
that's familiar to them so get them used
他们很熟悉，所以让他们习惯
to using Java idioms in an environment
在环境中使用Java习惯用法
as comfortable to them rather than
对他们来说舒适而不是
trying to get them up skilled on a new
试图使他们掌握新技能
language with new idioms on a new domain
在新域上具有新习语的语言
on a new project so the idea of doing
在一个新项目上，这样的想法
refactoring in order to obscure team is
重构以使团队难以理解
also a valid thing to choose it doesn't
选择它也是一件有效的事情
really matter which of these goals you
真正重要的是您要实现这些目标
choose but the idea is is to have in
选择，但想法是要有
your head what you're trying to achieve
你想要达到的目标
by doing this you're factoring and stick
通过这样做，您可以分解并坚持
to that you should limit the scope of
您应该限制范围
any refactoring you're doing in these
您在这些中所做的任何重构
examples were largely going to look at
例子主要是看
the method level so they're going to be
方法级别，因此它们将是
small and small bits of refactoring that
重构的一小部分
we're doing that has fairly limited
我们这样做的范围非常有限
scope and you might want to restrict
范围，您可能想限制
things either to a method level or class
方法级别或类的东西
level and we certainly shouldn't go
水平，我们当然不应该去
straight in and try to refactor the
直接进入并尝试重构
whole code base to use optional for
整个代码库使用可选的
example you really want to bring friends
例子，你真的想带朋友
the area that you're doing these
您正在做这些的区域
refactorings in the code base were going
在代码库中进行重构
to be looking at is a project called
要看的是一个名为
morphia this is an object document
morphia这是一个对象文档
mapper for MongoDB and there's a few
MongoDB的映射器，有一些
reasons why I've chosen this firstly
我首先选择这个的原因
because I was working on it when I was
因为我当时在做这件事
working at MongoDB so it's a code base I
在MongoDB工作，所以这是我的代码库
know very well but more interestingly
非常了解，但更有趣
it's an open source code base so that
这是一个开放源代码库，因此
you can take a look at it for yourself
你可以自己看看
see their before and after the
看他们之前和之后
refactorings it's also a fairly mature
重构也相当成熟
piece of code so it has a lot of the
一段代码，所以它有很多
same characteristics you'll probably
您可能会拥有的相同特征
find inside a lot of your own code bases
在很多自己的代码库中找到
sort of bits of code that maybe have
可能有的一些代码
evolved in a sub optimal way over time
随着时间的推移以次优的方式进化
or bits of code where it's no longer
或不再存在的一些代码
sort of fashionable to follow those ways
遵循这些方式的一种时尚
of doing stuff so it's quite a nice code
做事情，所以这是一个很好的代码
base for refactoring is you can look at
重构的基础是您可以查看
some of these and use chunks of code and
其中一些并使用代码块和
think of better ways to do these things
想出更好的方法来做这些事情
especially using Java 8 so without
特别是在使用Java 8的情况下
further ado let's dive straight in and
事不宜迟，让我们直接深入探讨
start doing some refactoring the first
开始做一些重构
thing I want to look at is refactoring
我想看的是重构
to using lambda expressions because this
使用lambda表达式，因为
is probably the simplest and most
可能是最简单，最
automated refactoring that we can do the
自动重构，我们可以做到
easiest things that we can do the
我们可以做的最简单的事情
easiest things
最简单的事情
can do is take the take any any
可以做的是随身携带
anonymous inner classes that implemented
实现的匿名内部类
things like comparator runnable callable
比较器可运行可调用
predicate all of these interfaces that
断言所有这些接口
always only have a single abstract
总是只有一个摘要
method and use give lambda expressions
方法和使用给定lambda表达式
instead of using anonymous inner type so
而不是使用匿名内部类型
let's go straight into our code what
让我们直接进入我们的代码
I've done is I've run inspections on the
我已经完成了对
morphia codebase I'll take a quick look
morphia代码库，我将快速浏览
at this because I'm in a fortunate
因为我很幸运
situation where I can actually show some
我可以实际显示一些情况
of the IntelliJ specific features in
中的IntelliJ特定功能
this webinar so I've got a I've got
这次网络研讨会，所以我有一个
inspections profile called Java eight
视察档案称为Java八
and I've selected a subset of the
并且我选择了
inspections most of the ones that I'm
检查我大部分的人
interested in are in the let's find it
对我们感兴趣的是找到它
so I'm in Java most of the ones I care
所以我大部分时间都在Java中
about are in the where is it
大约在哪里
I've gone right past it language level
我已经超过了语言水平
migration AIDS so here we have things
迁移艾滋病，所以我们这里有东西
like we are selecting to find anonymous
就像我们选择寻找匿名者一样
inter types that can be replaced with
可以替换为inter的类型
lambda expressions there's a whole bunch
lambda表达式有很多
of stuff around how we can replace lips
我们如何可以代替嘴唇
to the streams API and a lot of other
到流API以及许多其他
features here so this is the sort of
这里的功能，这是那种
main set of inspections we're going to
我们要进行的主要检查
be running I'm running a few more and
正在运行，我正在运行一些，
we'll see those as we come along but
我们会看到这些，但是
this is where you want to configure them
这是您要配置它们的地方
so in inspections in a language level
所以在语言水平的检查中
migration AIDS you might want to turn
您可能想转向的艾滋病
some of those on now I've already run
我现在已经跑了一些
those let's have a quick look at the
那些让我们快速看一下
first set this is anonymous type can be
首先设置这是匿名类型可以
replaced with lambda and if we look at
用lambda代替，如果我们看一下
this example we can see this is a
这个例子我们可以看到这是一个
predicate a guava predicate and we have
谓词番石榴谓词，我们有
our anonymous it in a type with our own
我们以自己的类型匿名
method and IntelliJ can just
方法和IntelliJ可以
automatically turn that straight into a
自动将其变成一个
lambda expression so that's a fairly
lambda表达式，所以这是一个相当
straightforward piece of magic whereby
直截了当的魔法
we are going to remove all the
我们将删除所有
boilerplate of our class declaration our
我们班级声明的样板
method our type information and just
方法我们的类型信息，只是
keep just a business logic just the
保持业务逻辑
stuff that we care about and
我们关心的东西
that into a lambda expression let me
变成lambda表情让我
show you another couple of examples I
再给我看几个例子
think with the maturity that Java eight
用Java的成熟思考八
is that probably most people in this
可能是大多数人
webinar have already come across these
网络研讨会已经遇到了这些
things so I'm going to skim quite
事情，所以我要去浏览一下
quickly over some the introductory level
快速入门
stuff so here's another example this is
东西，所以这是另一个例子
an example where we have a runnable and
一个例子，其中我们有一个可运行的
again the runner ball can be converted
再次可以将亚军球转换
into a lambda expression and here we
变成lambda表达式，在这里我们
just get the we just keep the core of
只是得到我们就保持核心
what the run method is what's a little
运行方法是什么
bit more of an interesting example is
一个有趣的例子是
this callable here has two lines so when
这个可调用在这里有两行，所以当
we shrink this down to a lambda
我们将其缩小为lambda
expression you can see the two lines in
表达式中您可以看到两行
the lambda in the lambda expression and
lambda表达式中的lambda和
what I prefer to do personally is I like
我喜欢亲自做的是我喜欢
to extract these into a method and give
将它们提取为一种方法并给出
it a description so this is until ten
这是一个描述，直到十点
items found and as this gives me a
找到项目，因为这给了我一个
couple of benefits one I can shrink my
几个好处之一，我可以缩小我的
lambda expression right down and I can
Lambda表达向下，我可以
also even maybe turn that into the
甚至可能把它变成
method reference if the if the call is
方法参考，如果调用是
is the correct shape but mainly this is
是正确的形状，但主要是
much more descriptive so now I can say
更具描述性，所以现在我可以说
until ten items found so it's much
直到找到十个物品，所以很多
clearer to me what these two lines of
我更清楚这两行
code is doing on top of that if I have
如果有的话，代码是最重要的
any errors I want to debug this it's a
我想调试的任何错误是
bit easier to debug lambda expressions
调试lambda表达式要容易一些
if they're actually inside a method so
如果它们实际上在方法内部，那么
that's that's my main reason for making
那是我制作的主要原因
my lambda expressions a single line lock
我的lambda表达式单行锁定
so that's all fairly straightforward
所以这很简单
what's kind of more interesting is we
更有趣的是我们
can those examples are anonymous inner
那些例子可以匿名吗
classes that were implementing an
正在实施
interface we can do the same thing with
界面，我们可以做同样的事情
abstract classes but we have to go one
抽象类，但我们必须走一个
step further so runnable let's take a
再往前走，让我们快点走
look at runnable oh that's not the right
看着可运行的哦，那不对
shortcut so run a ball
捷径，所以跑个球
functional interfaces in the interface
接口中的功能接口
with a single abstract method and if I
一个单一的抽象方法，如果我
look in my code I can find abstract
看我的代码，我可以找到摘要
methods that look fairly similar so I
看起来很相似的方法，所以我
have an abstract method with a single
有一个单一的抽象方法
abstract a with an abstract class with a
抽象与抽象类
single abstract method on it and
单一的抽象方法就可以了
IntelliJ suggesting that you can convert
IntelliJ建议您可以转换
this to an interface which I'm going to
这到我要去的界面
do and then once I've converted that to
然后将其转换为
an interface I can tag it with
我可以用它标记的界面
functional interface and then what I can
功能界面，然后我可以
do is I can go around and look at the
我可以四处看看
implementers of this and now I can turn
实现者，现在我可以转向
these into lambda expressions now I can
现在我可以将它们转换为lambda表达式
do that before because lambda
这样做是因为lambda
expressions don't what would abstract
表达式不是抽象的
classes only with interfaces so that's
类仅具有接口，因此
just an additional step that we can do
只是我们可以做的一个额外步骤
so those two things are just taking your
所以这两件事只是把你的
existing code and applying basically new
现有代码并基本上应用新的
syntax to the existing functionality
现有功能的语法
that you had so let's have a look at
你有，所以让我们来看看
that performance here we've got one of
在这里的表演，我们有一个
those examples so anonymous in a class
那些在课堂上如此匿名的例子
and our lambda expression and these the
和我们的lambda表达式，这些
two things we're going to compare in our
我们将要比较的两件事
performance test so in our performance
性能测试，因此在我们的性能中
tests were measuring operations for
测试正在测量操作
millisecond so more operations is better
毫秒，所以更多的操作更好
so I've got my smiley face at the top to
所以我的笑脸在顶部
remind me which is the better
提醒我哪个更好
performance so here we can see the
性能，所以在这里我们可以看到
lambda expression outperforms in an
lambda表达式在
anonymous inner class not by a lot it's
匿名内部类不是很多
kind of fairly equivalent but the lambda
相当相当，但lambda
expression is better performance now
表情现在表现更好
obviously Oracle is a lot of performance
显然，Oracle具有很多性能
testing around lambda expressions and
测试lambda表达式，并
there are lots of different types of
有很多不同类型的
anonymous inner classes and lambda
匿名内部类和lambda
expressions so the performance of them
表达式，所以它们的表现
varies according to what you're doing so
根据您的操作而变化
if you are interested in the ins and
如果您对ins和
outs of this you can follow this link
您可以点击此链接
here and that will take you to a much
在这里，那将带您到很多地方
more in-depth document about performance
关于性能的更深入的文档
testing new things in this particular
测试新事物
example you can see sometimes the lambda
示例，您有时会看到lambda
expression which is the one in this
这是一个表达
little reddish color is better than the
略带红色的颜色比
anonymous in attacks and sometimes it's
匿名攻击，有时是
not better so the answer is generally
不太好，所以答案通常是
the performance is fairly similar but
性能相当相似，但
it's not exactly the same
不完全一样
in terms of the performance analysis our
在性能分析方面
lambda expressions faster than or slower
Lambda表达式快于或慢于
than anonymous inner types well they're
比匿名内部类型好
more or less the same which means that
大致相同，这意味着
you can go ahead and refactor this
您可以继续进行重构
automatically without worrying too much
自动运行而不必担心太多
about it and but if it really matters
关于它，但是如果真的很重要
then obviously you want to measure each
那么显然你想衡量每个
individual instance to make sure that
个别实例以确保
it's not adding some performance
它没有增加一些性能
overhead now that was a straight
开销，这是直的
replacement of anonymous in the types to
将匿名类型替换为
lambda expressions what's more
lambda表达式，还有更多
interesting is some of the patterns we
有趣的是我们的一些模式
can follow now that we have the ability
现在可以跟随，因为我们有能力
to pass around behavior and not just
绕过行为而不仅仅是
object so we're going to find some
对象，所以我们要找到一些
places in our code where we can start
我们代码中可以开始的地方
passing lambda expressions what I've
传递lambda表达式我所拥有的
done is I've created a structural search
完成是我创建了结构搜索
and let's take a look at the structural
让我们看一下结构
search so I've created a search which is
搜索，所以我创建了一个搜索
going to look for a call on log of any
要寻找任何日志的呼叫
level with any message and what I want
与任何消息和我想要的水平
to do is I want to replace this with
我要做的是用
something which takes a lambda
需要lambda的东西
expression and I'll show you why in a
表达，我会告诉你为什么
minute if we look at one example of
分钟，如果我们看一个例子
these we're doing a log debug now
这些我们现在正在进行日志调试
normally in most of your code bases
通常在大多数代码库中
you'll seem to something like this if
你会看起来像这样
look is debug enabled then do that and
看看是否启用了调试，然后执行该操作
the reason does the reason for that
原因是为什么
because obviously the the the check that
因为很明显的检查
it could be inside the debug method and
它可能在debug方法中，
in fact probably is as well but the
实际上可能也是，但是
reason to wrap it in the if statement
将其包装在if语句中的原因
here is that here you're actually
这就是你在这里
building up a string you're creating a
建立一个字符串，您正在创建一个
new string in this case this Stages
在这种情况下，这是新字符串
field is a list so it goes off to that
字段是一个列表，所以它就可以了
list and builds up a string which curt
列出并建立一个字符串
which is a representation of all the
这是所有
items in that list and then append it to
该列表中的项目，然后将其附加到
the stages thing I'm n calls to debug
我要调试的阶段事物
method with that string now if you're in
现在，使用该字符串的方法
production you are probably not looking
您可能不希望生产
at debug level so you've just incurred
在调试级别，因此您已经产生了
the cost of building up that string when
何时建立该字符串的成本
you don't need it because you're not
您不需要它，因为您不需要
actually logging at that level now we're
实际以该级别进行记录
going to talk I'll turn
我去谈谈
we're doing this so if instead we pass
我们这样做是为了如果我们通过
in a lambda expression what we're doing
在lambda表达式中，我们在做什么
here is we're passing in the recipe of
这是我们传递的食谱
how to create that string but we're not
如何创建该字符串，但我们不是
creating that string just yet we're
创建那个字符串，我们
going to do it lazily so let me remove
懒惰地去做，所以让我删除
this here by the way if you want to know
如果您想知道的话，这里
what what shortcuts I'm using they are
我正在使用什么快捷方式
flashing up down the bottom of the
向下闪烁
screen you can see which shortcuts I'm
屏幕上可以看到我使用的快捷方式
using to to try and navigate quickly so
习惯于尝试快速导航，因此
here I'm going to create this method
在这里，我将创建此方法
it's going to take a supplier of string
这将需要一个字符串供应商
let's call it string supplier this
我们称它为字符串供应商
logger interface is implemented by a
记录器界面由
number of different implementations now
现在的不同实现数量
what I don't want to do is I don't want
我不想做的是我不想
to go into every single one of those
进入其中的每一个
implementations and create the same
实现并创建相同的
implementation of this debug method
此调试方法的实现
because I actually know what this debug
因为我实际上知道这个调试
message should do so let's create
消息应该这样做，让我们创建
another thing which is new in Java eight
Java 8中的另一项新功能
a default to method on my interface and
我界面上的默认方法
this whoops I've accidentally got with
我不小心跟了
that and then this default method is I'm
那然后这个默认方法是
going to do the check for whether the
要检查是否
debug is enabled there and then I'm
调试在那里启用，然后我
going to do debug string supplier yet
要去调试字符串供应商呢
now the difference here is that it's
现在的区别是
only at this point that we build up that
只有在这一点上，我们建立
string so it's only at this point we
字符串，所以仅在这一点上
incur the cost of creating that string
产生创建该字符串的成本
and what's nice about putting this as a
而将其作为
default method is that this is now
默认方法是现在
inherited by all of the implementations
由所有实现继承
of this interface I don't have to put
我不必放这个接口
that implementation on all the
在所有的实施
individual instance implementations so
个体实例的实现
that's good for performance reasons
出于性能考虑，这很好
we'll have a look at the performance so
我们来看看性能
you'll see that in a minute
一会儿你会看到
but what it's also good for is reducing
但它的好处是减少
things like copy and paste errors let me
复制和粘贴错误之类的东西让我
show you an example of this
给你看一个例子
so here's an example of a debug
所以这是一个调试的例子
statement that's in the code and it says
代码中的语句，它说
log dot is Trace enabled but it actually
日志点已启用跟踪，但实际上
logs with info level this is not
记录的信息级别不是
uncommon in terms of copy-paste errors
就复制粘贴错误而言并不常见
the fact that we're going to copy this
我们要复制这个事实
from somewhere else and then maybe
从其他地方开始
change the level of the look and now
改变外观水平，现在
that we can actually pass this in as now
我们实际上可以像现在这样传递
we're doing the if statement inside the
我们正在内部的if语句
info Court for example then I don't need
例如信息法院，那么我不需要
this and I know that I'm doing the right
这个，我知道我做对了
thing inside the method so I'm reducing
方法内部的东西，所以我减少了
these copy/paste
这些复制/粘贴
errors by passing these lambda
通过传递这些lambda错误
expressions around so not only do we
周围的表情，所以我们不仅
have an impact on performance but we
对性能有影响，但我们
also are potentially reducing some of
也有可能减少
the errors too so let's look at the
错误也是如此，让我们看一下
performance of this here I've got a
我在这里的表现
performance test which is testing for
性能测试
different cases one where I'm I'm
我在不同的情况下
logging with a constant string which is
用一个常量字符串记录
always the same thing - when I'm logging
总是一样的东西-当我登录时
with a lambda expression which also has
带有lambda表达式
a constant string before the third one
第三个字符串之前的常量字符串
we're logging with a string which is
我们使用的字符串是
changing I'm going to be appending some
改变我将要追加一些
new value to the end of that and you can
新价值到此为止，您可以
see it's just a really simple change and
看到这只是一个非常简单的更改，
the third one the fourth one where I'm
第三个人我第四个人
passing a lambda expression with the
与传递lambda表达式
same thing but this one will be lazily
同样的事情，但这个会很懒
evaluated inside the look so that if we
评估外观，以便我们
are not logging that string we don't
没有记录我们没有的字符串
incur the cost of creating it and we can
产生创建它的成本，我们可以
see here that the performance here is
看到这里的表现是
that it is very significant when we
当我们
actually have to create the string that
实际上必须创建一个字符串
we don't need we get very poor
我们不需要我们变得很贫穷
performance from that particular test so
该特定测试的性能
that by introducing relating evaluation
通过引入相关评估
using lambda expressions we have got
使用lambda表达式
quite a quick win for performance in our
在我们的表现中赢得了相当快的胜利
code so this is a good thing to do we
代码，所以这是一件好事
should definitely try and think about
绝对应该考虑一下
where we can use lambda expressions for
我们可以在其中使用lambda表达式
lazy evaluation that's kind of all I
我所有的那种懒惰的评价
really wanted to talk about explicitly
我真的很想明确地谈论
around lambda expressions I've got way
关于lambda表达式，我有办法
more to talk about around collections
更多关于收藏的话题
and streams because there's quite a lot
和流，因为有很多
of opportunities for refactoring to
重构的机会
using the new methods on collections and
在集合上使用新方法
the streams API the file
流API文件
and simplest thing to do is basically
最简单的事情基本上是
find everywhere where you are using a
随处找到您正在使用的
for loop before and replace it with a
之前的for循环并将其替换为
for each method now collections
现在每种方法的集合
themselves have a for each on and so you
自己每个都有一个，所以你
don't necessarily have to use the
不一定必须使用
streams API so sometimes it's dot stream
流API，所以有时它是点流
dot for each and sometimes it will be
每个点，有时会是
simply a dot for each on your collection
只是每个集合上的一个点
and we'll see different examples of
我们将看到不同的例子
these let's go back to our code here
这些让我们回到这里的代码
what we've got is we're looking for
我们所要寻找的是
loops can be collapsed with the stream
循环可以与流折叠
API if we look at our first example here
API，如果我们看这里的第一个示例
it says this can be collapsed with a for
它说可以用for折叠
each so if I do this
每一个，如果我这样做
enter replace it with a for each then
输入，然后用分别替换
I've quite simply removed my for loop
我已经完全删除了for循环
entirely and just replaced it with a for
完全替换为
each with the name of the method I want
每个都有我想要的方法的名称
to call for every entity in that set now
立即召集该集合中的每个实体
I can go one step further now because I
我现在可以再走一步，因为我
realize that this entity's variable is
意识到这个实体的变量是
only used here so I'm going to inline
仅在这里使用，所以我要内联
this and then once again this our
这个，然后再这个，我们的
variable is going to used here so I'm
变量将在这里使用，所以我
going to inline that as well
也要内联
so I've actually just removed a lot of
所以我实际上已经删除了很多
boilerplate there and all I'm really
样板，我真的
doing is infer this for loop I use a for
这样做是推断此for循环，我使用for
each and I'm going to call this this map
每个，我将称之为这张地图
method here so it's quite quite simple
这里的方法非常简单
example let's take a look at a slightly
例子让我们看一下
more complicated example here we have a
更复杂的例子在这里，我们有一个
for loop followed by a for loop followed
for循环后跟for循环
by an if statement and inside this if
在if语句中，在if中
statement we're going to add things to
声明我们将要添加的东西
another collection so let's see what
另一个收藏，让我们看看
IntelliJ suggests we can replace
IntelliJ建议我们可以更换
with this with a foot each now let's
现在，每个人都用脚
dissect this a little bit our faller has
剖析一下我们的坠落者
been replaced with a foot each if has
如果有的话，用脚代替
found its way into the filter we are
发现进入过滤器的方式
calling this on a stream and we're
在流上调用它，我们
actually using map to create this new
实际使用地图来创建这个新的
constraint violation thing which is the
约束违反的东西是
thing that needs to get added into our
需要添加到我们的东西
set so if we've collapsed is for and if
设置为如果我们崩溃了，则为
into a filter map and for each call now
进入过滤器地图，并针对每个呼叫
I'd be tempted to simplify this a little
我很想简化一下
bit more just for readability I might
只是为了提高可读性，我可能
call as create violations but that's
称为违反创建行为，但这就是
totally up to you really so we've
完全取决于您，所以我们
managed to simplify that code a little
设法简化了代码
bit but we still have this outer loop
一点，但我们仍然有这个外循环
here so for me I would look at this and
在这里，对我来说，我会看这个
think well maybe there's something
想得好，也许有些事
around the design which isn't great
周围的设计不是很好
because what we're doing here is we're
因为我们在这里做的是
passing in another collection and then
传入另一个集合，然后
doing some iterations multiple
做多次迭代
iterations because we're iterating here
迭代，因为我们在这里迭代
this is effectively an iteration and
这实际上是一个迭代，
then we're adding stuff into another
然后我们将东西添加到另一个
collection so I would look at this and
收集，所以我会看看这个和
I'll be thinking well perhaps nice
我会很好想，也许很好
refactoring needs to take a step up take
重构需要加强
a step back from this and look at the
退后一步，看看
methods which are calling this method to
调用此方法的方法
see if things can be restructured to be
看看事情是否可以重组为
able to do this in a single stream
能够在单个流中做到这一点
operation let's look at another example
操作让我们看另一个例子
here we have an if statement our for
这里我们有一个if语句
loop another if statement for loop and
循环另一个if语句进行循环和
then an if and an else this is quite a
然后，如果和其他，这是一个相当
complex piece of logic now because we
现在，逻辑很复杂，因为我们
have an if and an else we have two code
有一个if和else我们有两个代码
paths set so we know that this can't be
设置了路径，所以我们知道这不可能
collapsed down into a single stream
崩溃成一条小溪
operation inside here but we'll see what
在这里进行操作，但我们将看到
we can do here now IntelliJ has taken a
我们现在可以在这里做IntelliJ已经采取了
look at
看着
decided it can do a slightly more
决定可以做更多一点
complex thing so because we've got two
复杂的事情，因为我们有两个
four loops we've effectively ended up
我们已经有效地结束了四个循环
with a four each and a flat map and the
每个有四个，还有一个平面图，
flat map is is as a result of that
平面图是由于
second that second fall is there and the
第二个第二个秋天在那里，
if statement has been reflected towards
如果陈述已经反映到
the filter so we actually have the same
过滤器，所以我们实际上有相同的
functionality the same features just in
功能相同的功能就在
using the streams API so what's
使用流API，这是什么
interesting here is to performance test
有趣的是性能测试
the difference between me the classical
我与古典之间的区别
for loop and the new for each whether
for循环和每个是否新
you're using streams or not so this is
您是否在使用流，所以这是
our first example our simple example
我们的第一个例子我们的简单例子
where we replaced this for with a simple
我们用一个简单的替换它
call to forage and here we find the
打电话给草料，在这里我们找到
performance is pretty much exactly the
性能几乎就是
same so we don't really need to worry
一样，所以我们真的不需要担心
too much about whether we decide to do
关于我们是否决定做太多
this or not there's more complex example
这个或没有一个更复杂的例子
which uses the flat map as well as a
使用平面地图以及
filter again the performance is kind of
再次过滤性能是一种
more less the same so we can make
更多更少相同，所以我们可以使
decisions as to whether we want to do
关于我们是否要做的决定
this use fracturing based on performance
这种基于性能的压裂
we could say it doesn't really matter we
我们可以说这并不重要，我们
can apply this refactoring if you want
如果需要，可以应用此重构
to but we still have to look at this and
到，但我们仍然要看这个
decide whether we think this is more
决定我们是否认为这还更多
readable because we do still have
可读，因为我们仍然有
another if statement outside here and we
另一个if语句在这里，我们
do have this quite ugly if-else inside
里面确实有这个丑陋的if-else
here so to me there's room in terms of
所以对我来说，有空间
readability there's room for additional
可读性还有余地
refactoring there we can expect the IDE
在那里重构，我们可以期待IDE
should just magically do this for us
应该为我们神奇地做到这一点
and a third example where we remove this
还有第三个例子，我们删除了这个
full openness if statement into a filter
完全开放的if语句进入过滤器
and map the performance here is quite a
并在这里映射性能相当
bit worse on the reflected code but it's
反映的代码更糟，但这是
not happy it does about half the amount
不开心大约占一半
of operations per millisecond it's not a
每毫秒的操作数
factor of ten but it's a it's not as not
十分之一，但这不是
ideal there it's not exactly the same
理想的地方不完全一样
performance and this might seem quite
性能，这似乎很不错
puzzling because it's still doing the
令人困惑，因为它仍然在做
same thing as some of the other examples
和其他一些例子一样
in fact arguably it's doing slightly
实际上可以说它在做些微
less because there's no flat map and
更少，因为没有平面图
it's not a such complex example however
这不是一个如此复杂的例子
if you look at the performance of these
如果你看看这些的表现
this one for example we're getting
举例来说，我们正在
nought point six operations per
零点每操作六个
millisecond which is not very many
毫秒不是很多
operations so it could be that the thing
操作，所以可能是那件事
was happening for the loop is quite
发生的循环是相当
expensive and
昂贵和
iterating over the loop is not the most
遍历循环不是最
expensive thing in this code therefore
因此，这段代码中昂贵的东西
whether you use a for loop or a for each
无论您使用for循环还是每个
doesn't really impact your overall
并不会真正影响您的整体
performance whereas here you're getting
性能，而在这里
nearly a thousand operations per second
每秒近一千次操作
in which case it might be that using the
在这种情况下，可能是使用
streams API has added an additional
流API已添加了其他功能
overhead to this to this iterating over
为此的开销
these in particular so is it is it a
这些特别是它
given that you're going to refactor any
鉴于您将重构任何
for loop into using a for each well no
for循环为每个孔使用a
sometimes it's going to be foreign
有时候会很外国
performance wise and sometimes you're
明智的表现，有时你
going to have to think about whether it
不得不考虑是否
gives you anything in terms of
给你任何东西
readability or performance the next
可读性或性能下
thing that's quite straightforward to
很简单的事情
refactor is turning a for loop into a
重构将for循环变成了
collect payment so if we have a look at
收款，所以如果我们看看
this example now here we have a slight
这个例子现在我们在这里
complication in that our what we're
复杂之处在于我们
doing is we're iterating over a list of
我们要做的是遍历
keys and we're adding the IDS into a
键，我们将IDS添加到
list of ID's so this sounds like a
ID的列表，所以听起来像是
classic problem for collect
收集的经典问题
however this ArrayList is being
但是这个ArrayList正在
initialized with an initial capacity
用初始容量初始化
which can't which means that encourage a
这不能意味着鼓励
can't automatically turn it into a
不能自动将其变成
collect statement so I'm going to assume
收集陈述，所以我要假设
that this works in red to test to see
可以用红色测试以查看
whether this has any performance impact
这是否对性能有影响
so to begin with I'm going to remove
所以首先我要删除
that initial capacity so that I can
初始容量，以便我可以
refactor this more easily now I can
现在我可以更轻松地重构它了
replace that with a collect statement
用collect语句代替
and I end up with a kind of classic
最后我得到了一种经典
collect where I'm going to map from the
收集我要从中映射的位置
key just get the ID and return a list of
键只是获取ID并返回列表
ID's from this list of keys let's look
此键列表中的ID让我们来看一下
at another example
在另一个例子
so in this example we're doing something
所以在这个例子中，我们正在做一些事情
fairly similar
相当相似
we are populating a list of valid fields
我们正在填充有效字段的列表
with some subset of fields from this
与此相关的一些字段子集
fields list and we can actually see what
字段列表，我们实际上可以看到
we're trying to do we're going to ignore
我们正在尝试做，我们将忽略
static and final fields so let's get
静态字段和最终字段，让我们开始吧
IntelliJ to replace the places with a
IntelliJ将场所替换为
collect statement now what I would like
现在收集我想要的陈述
to do is I'd like to get rid of this
我要做的就是摆脱这个
comment because the comment says the
发表评论，因为评论说
codes not really very clear so in fact
代码不是很清楚，所以实际上
what we can do is we can improve this by
我们可以做的就是通过
extracting that inter methods let's call
提取方法间的调用
this is not static or final and then we
这不是静态的还是最终的，然后我们
can get rid of this comment completely I
可以完全摆脱此评论我
would argue that in this case this is
会认为在这种情况下，这是
more readable so we're filtering out the
更具可读性，因此我们正在过滤掉
only things that we want a fields that
只有我们想要的东西
are not static or final and we're
不是静态的还是最终的，我们是
collecting news into a new list and
将新闻收集到新列表中，以及
returning that list so it's a bit more
返回该列表，所以还有更多
readable than it was before we've also
可读性比以前还高
removed from the boilerplate and
从样板中取出并
obviously there's comments so let's look
显然有评论，让我们来看
at the
在
to this the first example what I wanted
对于这个第一个例子我想要什么
to do as I mentioned is I want to
正如我提到的那样要做
performance test whether this initial
性能测试是否初始
array allocation has any impact on
数组分配对
performance so I'm testing it with the
性能，所以我正在用
array allocation and without it and then
数组分配，没有它，然后
I'm testing the refactored code with the
我正在使用
map and play and what we find in this
地图和游戏以及我们在此发现的内容
particular case for a list of ten
十个清单的特殊情况
elements which isn't very many that the
不是很多的元素
original code with the pre allocation of
预先分配的原始代码
the of the ArrayList size is much more
ArrayList大小的更大
performant than any of the other
表现比其他任何一个
examples it performs better than the
比它表现更好的例子
simplified code without the array size
没有数组大小的简化代码
it performs better than the refactored
它的性能比重构的要好
code and parallel with ten items
代码并与十项并行
basically let's not even talk about it
基本上我们甚至不谈论它
doesn't even appear on the chart if we
如果我们甚至没有出现在图表上
add a few more elements into the list
在列表中添加更多元素
that we're iterating over so in this
我们正在迭代中
case 10,000 elements then we see that
案例10,000个元素，那么我们看到
the initial allocation of the list size
列表大小的初始分配
really starts to make very little
真的开始变得很少
difference and parallel starts to become
差异和并行开始成为
much more performance but our refactor
性能更高，但我们的重构
code is still not performing quite as
代码仍然不能像
well as the other examples again when I
以及其他例子，当我
put my orders of magnitude but it is it
把我的数量级，但就是
is a it does perform a little bit poorer
是它的确性能稍差
the other example we looked at here
我们在这里看到的另一个例子
weren't being able to get rid of this
不能摆脱这个
comment by replacing it with a filter
用过滤器替换评论
intellect now here the refactor code
现在在这里智能化重构代码
performs worse than the original code as
表现比原始代码差
well in this case I think it's because
在这种情况下，我认为是因为
you're doing in a raised dot stream so
你在凸起的点流中做
you're using you had code that was an
您正在使用的代码是
array and and now you're having to do
数组，现在您必须要做
arrays upstream so it's probably not
上游的数组，所以可能不是
going to be as an efficient we'll talk a
成为一种高效的我们将谈论
little bit more about this a little bit
关于这一点
later on
稍后的
so automatically turning your code from
所以自动从
a for loop into a collect statement and
for循环到collect语句中，
you're going to have to be careful a
您将必须小心a
little bit about the performance of that
关于那个性能的一点点
code so if you if you if you really care
代码，如果您愿意的话
about performance you probably gonna
关于你可能要表现的
want to write some tests now here's a
现在要写一些测试
good time to talk a little bit or have a
是时候聊一点或有
little bit the caveat in the grand
一点小小的警告
scheme of things some of these
这些事情中的一些
performance implications may be pretty
性能影响可能是相当大的
much nothing like I said we're talking
没什么像我说的那样
about maybe half the speed
大概速度的一半
but we talk about micro benchmarks I'm
但是我们谈论的是微基准测试
benchmarking just this method in in this
只是在这种方法中进行基准测试
particular case this code actually is
特定情况下，此代码实际上是
about code which goes off to the
关于代码的
database so the cost of talking to a
数据库，因此与某人交谈的成本
database is probably substantially more
数据库可能更多
than the cost of adding and then some of
而不是添加成本，然后
the additional costs added by adding by
加上的额外费用
using the java 8 features so micro
使用Java 8功能如此微
benchmarks are useful but you have to
基准测试很有用，但您必须
consider stuff in this in the grand
考虑一下这个东西
scheme of the whole application which is
整个应用的方案是
why it's important for you to have
为什么对你来说很重要
performance tests automated performance
性能测试自动化性能
tests for the code package that matters
测试重要的代码包
the most to you
最给你的
now here's an area where I think streams
现在这是一个我认为溪流的区域
are very interesting where we can look
我们可以看的地方很有趣
at code which was previously a series of
在以前的一系列代码中
operations and collapse them down into a
操作并将其分解为
single stream operation here's our first
单流操作，这是我们的第一个
example we have a set subset here of
例如，我们在这里有一个集合子集
constraint violations whatever they are
约束违规，无论它们是什么
we're going to iterate over those add
我们将迭代这些添加
them into a new list and then we've sort
他们进入一个新列表，然后我们进行排序
that list and then we iterate over that
该列表，然后我们遍历该列表
list and do something with it so we
列出并做一些事情，所以我们
should be able to collapse this down to
应该能够将其分解为
a single stream operation so IntelliJ
单个流操作，因此IntelliJ
says that we can replace this with a
说我们可以用
collect statement note that it has
收集有
figured out that because you have a sort
弄清楚，因为你有一个排序
call here it can add sorted here and
调用这里它可以添加在这里排序
this is a fairly new piece of
这是一个相当新的
intelligence in IntelliJ some of the
IntelliJ中的智能
older versions don't make that leap so
较旧的版本不会飞跃
it's worth bearing in mind that if you
值得牢记的是，如果您
have a sort cord you want to make sure
有您要确保的分类线
that your stream operation is also
你的流操作也是
sorted and then what do we do so then we
排序，然后我们该怎么做，然后我们
take this list and then we iterate over
拿这个清单，然后我们迭代
it and do something so that seems to me
并做点什么让我觉得
like perhaps we can replaces
就像我们可以取代
straightforwardly
直接地
with a for each we'll do the same thing
每个都有一个，我们将做同样的事情
that the for loop was doing so we do log
for循环正在执行，因此我们进行记录
line dot log and of course we don't need
行点日志，当然我们不需要
to allocate this to anything because
分配给任何东西，因为
it's not doing anything anymore and then
它不再做任何事情，然后
we simply remove risk so
我们只是消除风险，所以
with we originally had an iteration here
我们最初在这里进行了迭代
some sort of iterating happening in the
在某种程度上发生的迭代
sort probably and another iteration
可能排序和另一个迭代
through the the list here and we've
通过这里的列表，我们已经
collapses down to a single stream
崩溃成一条小溪
operation so it's a bit neater and a bit
操作，所以它有点整洁
more understandable and hopefully we
更容易理解，希望我们
should see some sort of impact on a
应该会看到对
performance the second example here is
性能第二个例子是
in query in pull now this might not look
在查询中拉现在可能看起来不像
like multiple operations so what you're
喜欢多种操作，所以您
doing is you're iterating over this
要做的是您正在对此进行迭代
collection you're assigning stuff adding
您要分配的收藏集
them to another field list and then
他们到另一个字段列表，然后
you're doing fields to array and passing
你正在做字段数组和传递
that into another method so you're doing
变成另一种方法，所以你在做
at least two operations there one you're
至少有两个操作
iterating over a list in creating a new
在创建新列表时遍历列表
list and to you're then turning that
清单，然后你就把那个
list into an array we can actually see
列出一个我们可以实际看到的数组
what we can do to improve this again we
我们可以做些什么来再次改善我们
have an initial capacity on this list so
在此列表上具有初始容量，因此
it's not straightforward to turn it into
把它变成不是一件容易的事
a collect straightway I'm going to
我要去的一条收集路
remove that initial capacity and then
删除该初始容量，然后
I'm going to replace it it says replaced
我要替换它说替换
with two array now this is some magic
现在有两个阵列，这是一些魔术
that I think and this this particular
我认为，这个特殊的
refactoring did improve in IntelliJ
重构确实改善了IntelliJ
twenty sixteen point three and I think
二十六点三，我认为
it's got even smarter in 2017 point one
它在2017年变得更加智能
because when I demoed this last time I
因为当我最后一次演示时
still had to do some manual steps and
仍然需要做一些手动步骤
now I don't have to do any manual steps
现在我不必做任何手动操作
and what it's done is it's taken all of
它完成了所有的工作
my original code and pretty much
我原来的代码，差不多
completely rewritten it now I removed
完全重写了它，现在我删除了
this this size allocation to be
这个大小分配是
ArrayList it's using the get name to
ArrayList使用获取名称
store just putting that into a map and
存储只是将其放入地图中，
then it works out that what I've done
然后算出我所做的
here is I've added things into a list
这是我已将内容添加到列表中
and then I call to array so intelligence
然后我打电话给数组
collapsed that straight down into a to
倒塌成一个
array call and in lined that into the
数组调用并将其排入
retrieved fields method called as well
检索字段方法也称为
so there's quite a lot of stuff going on
所以有很多事情要做
and now you might want to do with some
现在您可能想要处理一些
of these operations you might want to do
这些操作中，您可能想执行
them in incremental steps to see what's
他们以逐步的步骤看什么
actually happening
实际发生
example where we had sort of three
这个例子，我们有三个
operations collapsed into one the
行动合而为一
performance here not surprisingly the
这里的表现不足为奇
refactored code performs better than the
重构的代码比
original code not by millions of orders
原始代码不是通过数百万个订单
of magnitude but it does perform better
数量级，但确实表现更好
this is good it's more readable and
这很好，它更具可读性，
margining more performance now this
现在可以提高性能
second example the like I said there's a
第二个例子，就像我说的那样
sub naive intermediate steps for
次幼稚的中间步骤
refactoring this where you might say I'm
重构这个地方，你可能会说我
going to collect everything into a list
要将所有内容收集到列表中
and then called to array on it so I
然后调用它的数组，所以我
wanted to performance test that to see
想测试一下性能
what the impact was here because this is
这是什么影响，因为这是
basically two operations we're going to
基本上我们要进行两个操作
collect and then a to array which is the
收集然后一个to数组是
same as the original code and then I
与原始代码相同，然后我
want to compare that against the new
想要将其与新产品进行比较
complete refactoring where we go
完全重构我们要去的地方
straight to two array and here we can
直接到两个数组，在这里我们可以
see that the naive refactoring with the
看到与
two steps doesn't perform as well as the
两步效果不如
other operations and the the fully
其他操作和全部
refactored one performs almost as well
重构的人几乎表现良好
as the original and this is a quite a
作为原始的，这是一个相当
high number of operations per second so
每秒的操作数很高，因此
this is quite a good refactoring in
这是一个很好的重构
escape I've had to say the performance
逃脱我不得不说的表现
analysis is inconclusive even though I'm
分析是不确定的，即使我
much happier with these results than the
这些结果比
other ones because again we're not
其他人，因为我们再次不是
talking about orders of magnitude better
更好地谈论数量级
but the the findings here is that we
但是这里的发现是
don't have a negative impact on
对...没有负面影响
performance by doing these particular
通过做这些特别的表现
refactoring now I've just got two more
现在重构，我只剩下两个
research things to show and then we're
研究要展示的东西，然后我们
going to sort of take apart some of the
会分解一些
some of the things that we found and
我们发现的一些东西
come to some conclusions this for loop
得出一些结论
to any match is a new refactoring which
任何匹配都是一种新的重构
came in in twenty sixteen point three
进来二十三点三
I'll show you an example
我举个例子
I'd lost it if you so any match is a
如果您如此匹配，我会输掉它
fairly straightforward operation it's
相当简单的操作
where you are going to be limping
你要行的地方
through some lists and as soon as you
通过一些列表，并尽快
find something which matches some
找到一些匹配的东西
criteria then you return a true or false
条件，然后您返回true或false
so this can be automatically turned into
所以可以自动变成
and any match operation here you can see
以及这里的任何匹配操作
again we just got rid of the the
再次，我们只是摆脱了
iteration code and kept the the main
迭代代码并保留主
core code that's in the if statement so
if语句中的核心代码
here I'm going to performance tests the
在这里，我要进行性能测试
difference between the original code the
原始代码之间的区别
the new code which is it's more readable
新代码更具可读性
but of course the interesting point
但当然有趣的一点
about a lot of these Java eight stream
这些Java八流中的很多
operations is the ability to paralyze
操作是瘫痪的能力
them so I'm going to performance test
他们，所以我要去性能测试
this against the parallel version as
这与并行版本相反
well
好
now the original code performs pretty
现在原始代码执行得很漂亮
well and the reflected Kurtis is for ten
好吧，反映出来的库尔蒂斯十个人
values in the list the original code
列表中的值原始代码
performs very well the refracted code is
执行很好的折射代码是
not even half the speed and parallel for
甚至没有一半的速度和并行
ten values is nowhere to be seen because
十个值无处可寻，因为
the cost is splitting up a ten value
成本分摊了十个值
list running over multiple cores and
列出运行在多个内核上的列表
then bringing the result back in is just
然后把结果带回来
far too much overhead for that number of
对于该数目的而言，开销太大了
values where it starts to get a little
值开始变小
bit more interesting is where you have
更有趣的是你在哪里
ten thousand values in this particular
一万个值
list but again we don't really see any
清单，但是我们再也看不到
great performance improvements here and
此处的性能大幅提升，并且
I think in this particular case I think
我认为在这种情况下，我认为
it's because we're using a raised dot
这是因为我们使用了凸起的圆点
stream and iteration over arrays is a
流和数组迭代是一个
much more it is a nice efficient thing
更重要的是，这是一件好事
to do for compilers and for the CPU it's
为编译器和CPU做的
a very predictable thing to do to do
做一件非常可预测的事情
anything with a straight array class and
任何带有直数组类的东西
so when you incur the cost of turning
因此，当您承担转弯的费用时
that into a stream start doing with
变成流开始与
objects you're going to end up with
你最终会遇到的对象
quite a lot of additional cost and you
相当多的额外费用，您
can see that in the performance here the
可以在这里的表演中看到
performance really suffers from using
使用确实会影响性能
streams instead of using the straight
流而不是使用直线
array and when we get to a hundred
数组，当我们达到一百
thousand values in here then with then
一千个值在这里然后
parallel starts that outperform we
并行开始表现优于我们
factored by quite a lot more both game
两者都有很多因素
are still not really seeing the
仍然没有真正看到
performance of using raw array
使用原始数组的性能
manipulation so any match I said
操作，所以我说的任何匹配
but it's not the fault of any match it's
但这不是任何比赛的错
actually the problem of using a raised
实际上是使用加注的问题
dot stream doing any sort of operation
点流执行任何类型的操作
on a raised dot stream is probably going
在凸起的点流上可能正在
to be much more expensive than doing
比做的要贵得多
operations directly either way
两种方式直接操作
particularly for smaller ways and find
特别是对于较小的方法和查找
first so this is a very similar thing to
首先，这是非常相似的事情
any match if I find my example this is
任何匹配，如果我找到我的例子，这是
again where we're going to iterate over
再一次，我们要迭代
some lists and once we find the first
一些列表，一旦我们找到第一个
thing which matches some criteria then
然后符合某些条件的东西
we're going to return that thing so we
我们要归还那东西，所以我们
can replace this with a fine first and
可以先将其替换为
in this case that's in line in line that
在这种情况下，
we are doing in a raised dot stream we
我们在凸起的点流中进行
could also slightly simplify this by
也可以通过
saying a stream of it does the same
说它的流确实一样
thing it just it kind of reduces the
事情只是减少了
amount of code on the screen so that's
屏幕上的代码量是
why I prefer that particular example and
为什么我喜欢那个特定的例子
so here yes again we've just removed
所以在这里，我们再次删除了
everything from the if statement and put
一切从if语句放
it into the filter another example of
它进入过滤器的另一个例子
this is in my converters I'm going to do
这是在我要使用的转换器中
the same thing here we are doing on the
我们在这里做的同样的事情
previous example we had to create our
前面的例子我们必须创建我们的
own stream of effective classes in this
自己的有效课程流
example I'll often
我经常
in this example
在这个例子中
we're doing a stream we're getting the
我们正在做一个流，我们正在
stream from this collection which is a
来自此收藏集的流
list and here we can see we are
列表，在这里我们可以看到我们
explicitly stating what to return if we
明确说明如果我们返回什么
don't find anything so there's some
什么都没找到所以有一些
readability gains there as well so let's
那里的可读性也有所提高，所以让我们
do a quick check of the performance of
快速检查性能
this fine first is again not performing
这个很好的第一又没有表现
quite as fast as the original in
与原始版本一样快
particular here because we're doing a
特别是在这里，因为我们正在做一个
raised stream and I wanted to test the
提高了流，我想测试
difference between doing a raised dot
凸起点之间的区别
stream and stream that off and the
流和流，然后
performance here is exactly the same so
这里的表现是完全一样的
pick whichever one suits you I'm in the
选择适合我的人
second example where we're using the
第二个例子，我们使用
streams API we again we just don't get
流API，我们再次没有得到
the same sort of performance that we've
与我们一样的表现
got from the original code for an array
从数组的原始代码中获得
of ten element as we start to get much
十个元素的数量，因为我们开始获得很多
bigger data that's where we start to see
我们开始看到的更大数据
the benefits of both going parallel and
并行和并行的好处
perhaps using the refactor code so again
也许再次使用重构代码
find first in terms of performance it's
在性能方面找到第一
worth testing that to see if you've got
值得测试，看看是否有
any field impact on your performance for
任何对您的绩效有影响的领域
that particularly for small arrays my
特别是对于小阵列
final example is remove if this is one
最后一个例子是删除，如果这是一个
of my favorite examples and I hope
我最喜欢的例子，我希望
you'll be able to see one here what I've
您将可以在这里看到我所拥有的
got is I've got some set helpfully
我有一些帮助
called s which I'm iterating over and
我正在迭代的称为s
then I'm pulling it right out of using a
然后我就从使用
while loop which happening for a while
发生一段时间的while循环
to remove everything from the iterator
从迭代器中删除所有内容
which matches some criteria and I can
符合某些条件，我可以
replace it straightforwardly with a
直接将其替换为
simple remove if we're passing the
如果我们通过了，则简单删除
parameter of the thing I really care
我真正关心的东西的参数
about and here we just get rid of all of
在这里，我们只是摆脱了所有
this nonsense of how to traverse the how
这种如何遍历的废话
to reverse the collection of how to get
扭转如何获得的集合
the next item we just don't care about
下一个我们不在乎的项目
that we just pass in the lambda
我们只是通过lambda
expression of remove everything which
表达删除一切
matches this particular pattern and if
匹配此特定模式，如果
we also have a look so here at you can
我们也来看看，所以在这里你可以
see I've just got rid of all that
看到我已经摆脱了所有这些
boilerplate if you look at the
样板，如果你看
performance it actually performs better
性能实际上表现更好
as well
以及
so out of all the refactorings here this
所以在这里所有的重构中
is my favorite one you get you get
是我最喜欢的一个
better performance and you get more
更好的性能，您可以获得更多
readability as well I've had to say
我也不得不说可读性
inconclusive because the performance is
没有定论，因为表现是
not so order of magnitude better that is
不那么好一个数量级
just marginally better in this
在这方面稍微好一点
particular case let's go through and
特殊情况下，我们来看一下
summarize each - because I kind of fund
总结每个-因为我是一种基金
a lot of different refactorings at you
您有许多不同的重构
and a lot of performance data so I
还有很多性能数据，所以我
really want to summarize those things
真的想总结一下这些东西
before before giving some sort of
在给予某种东西之前
conclusion about refactoring to Java
关于重构为Java的结论
eight and then after that there will be
八点之后
time for questions so refactoring to use
是时候提问了，以便重构
lambda expressions instead of for
Lambda表达式代替
example anonymous inner pipe is very
示例匿名内部管道非常
easy to automate and it's pretty safe
易于自动化，非常安全
performance wise you're going to get
性能上的明智之举
more or less the same sort of
差不多一样
performance so you can kind of under
性能，因此您可以根据
under most circumstances just go ahead
在大多数情况下，请继续
and do that without worrying too much
而且不用担心太多
designing for lambda expressions so for
为lambda表达式设计
example using lambda expressions for
使用lambda表达式的示例
lazy evaluation could give you a big
懒惰的评估可以给你很大的帮助
performance benefit in the example of
以性能为例
the logging example if you don't need to
记录示例，如果您不需要
incur the cost of building up the string
产生建立琴弦的费用
because you're not going to log it then
因为那你不打算记录它
wrap it inside a lambda expression and
将其包装在lambda表达式中，然后
you're going to get much better
你会变得更好
performance from that generally using
性能通常
the new idioms the new methods on
新习语上的新方法
collections the streams API lambda
收集流API lambda
expressions and so forth does increase
表情等等确实增加了
readability I've got a few examples here
可读性我这里有一些例子
for example obviously the obvious one is
例如，很明显，显而易见的是
lambda expressions versus anonymous
Lambda表达式与匿名
inner classes just removes all the type
内部类只删除所有类型
information that you don't really need
您真正不需要的信息
I'm using a collect instead of using a
我正在使用收集而不是使用
for loop and adding stuff is a little
for循环和添加东西有点
bit more descriptive the any match is
更具描述性的任何匹配是
again a bit more descriptive a bit less
再次多一些描述性，少一些
code but it's not so much about the a
代码，但与a无关
bit less code it's more about what is
更少的代码，更多的是关于什么
this thing doing well it's just telling
这件事做得很好，这只是在说
you if anything matches this particular
你，如果有什么与此特定
criteria and the same thing with fine
标准和相同的东西很好
first fine first just allows you to
第一好第一只是让你
state this is the thing we're looking
声明这是我们正在寻找的东西
for something with this annotation and
对于带有此注释的东西
of course remove if you just lose a
当然，如果您丢失了
whole lot of boilerplate and you're left
整个样板，你就离开了
with only the thing you care about
只关心你的事
only the pattern that you want to remove
仅您要删除的模式
and then when you
然后当你
doing multiple operations and tracking
进行多项操作和跟踪
those down into a single extreme
那些陷入单一的极端
operation you get quite a lot of wins so
操作，您将获得很多胜利，因此
instead of having to have two four loops
不必有两个四个循环
with the sort you have a single stream
与您只有一个流的排序
operation which does a map sorted and a
对地图进行排序的操作和
for each and so it's much more easy to
每一个，所以它更容易
reason around and probably a better
周围的原因，可能更好
performance and again here this is where
性能，这又是这里
we have we were doing multiple
我们有做过多次
operations without really realizing it
没有真正意识到它的操作
because we were collecting stuck into a
因为我们正在收集卡在
list and then doing a - array on it and
列出，然后对其执行-数组，并
here we'll just turn that into a single
在这里，我们将其变成一个
operation but you do need to be aware of
操作，但您确实需要注意
the performance now I'm not saying you
现在的表现我不是在说你
have to micro benchmark every single
必须对每个人进行微基准测试
instance of these of these refactorings
这些重构的实例
but you do need to have an understanding
但您确实需要了解
of which of them might have which of
他们当中哪个可能拥有哪个
them might have an impact on performance
它们可能会对性能产生影响
and which ones you might need to go away
以及您可能需要离开的
and check and test for for example
并检查和测试例如
anywhere we're going to be using a
我们将要使用的任何地方
raised extreme is probably going to be
提出极端
slower than using in a way as I said
比我说的要慢
operations on arrays are very efficient
数组上的操作非常有效
for computers they're easy to reason
对于计算机，他们很容易推理
around for the compiler is they're easy
对于编译器来说很容易
for the CPU to reason around and in
让CPU来回推理
memory all those array objects are next
存储所有这些数组对象
to each other - so array operations
彼此-数组操作
traversing arrays is a very efficient
遍历数组是非常有效的
operation so arrays dot stream may be
操作，以便数组点流可能是
taking away from efficiency and so this
失去效率，所以这
is one of those example where the using
是其中一个使用示例
arrays just gave you much worse
数组让你更糟
performance from the original code using
使用原始代码的性能
the for each or the collect might be
对于每个或收集可能是
slower than iterating over collection
比遍历集合慢
this is where the answer is it depends
这就是答案所在
so there are some cases where using the
因此在某些情况下
for each gave you sort of half of the
每个给你一半的
speed that you had had before in some
某些速度
cases in sorry some cases in the past
过去很遗憾的情况
where you get the same sort of
你会得到相同的
performance this is where it really it
性能才是真正的表现
depends a bit on what you're doing
取决于你在做什么
what's the cost of the operation inside
里面的手术费用是多少
that iteration and parallel is not going
迭代和并行不会进行
to magically give you speed improvements
神奇地提高您的速度
parallel is not some magic incantation
平行不是魔咒
which would just do all the hard work
这将完成所有艰苦的工作
for you it will give you speed
对你来说，它将给你速度
improvements if your data is very big
如果您的数据很大，则可以进行改进
for example here we've got 10,000
例如，这里有10,000
elements we're starting to see where
我们开始看到元素
parallelize is giving us some benefit
并行化给我们带来了一些好处
and if your operation is very expensive
如果您的手术非常昂贵
then you might want to use multiple CPUs
那么您可能想要使用多个CPU
and format
和格式
over multiple CPUs those the cases where
在多个CPU上的情况下
parallel is going to be useful for you
并行将对您有用
sometimes with these Java 8 features you
有时使用这些Java 8功能
get improved readability and better
获得更好的可读性和更好的
performance so for example it was the
性能，例如
remove if we got a better readability
如果可读性更好，请删除
and we got better performance as well so
而且我们也有更好的表现
let's conclude these should you migrate
让我们总结一下这些是否应该迁移
your code to Java 8 well of course it
您的Java 8代码当然很好
depends there's never a straightforward
取决于从来没有一个简单的方法
answer to to any technical question so
回答任何技术问题
it depends you have to remember what the
这取决于您必须记住
goal of your refactoring was was your
您重构的目标是
goal to get better performance in which
目标以获得更好的性能，其中
case obviously you're going to need to
情况显然，您将需要
test that performance if your goal was
如果您的目标是测试该性能
readability or learning then you need to
可读性或学习性，那么您需要
check whether the refactoring has given
检查重构是否已经给出
you better readability or whether you
更好的可读性或是否
have actually learned anything from
实际上从中学到了什么
doing use refactorings so you should be
使用重构，因此您应该
comparing the results of your research
比较研究结果
rings with the initial original goal
达到最初的初始目标
that you had in mind you need to
你需要记住的是
understand which things might impact
了解哪些事情可能会影响
performance like using a raised dot
性能像使用凸起的点
stream and if you're not really sure
流，如果您不确定
which things are going to impact
哪些事情会影响
performance you need to measure that
您需要衡量的性能
your tools like for example IntelliJ
您的工具，例如IntelliJ
IDEA can really help you automate a lot
IDEA可以真正帮助您实现很多自动化
of this process and can suggest things
这个过程，可以提出建议
to you that you didn't know was possible
给你，你不知道有可能
but you do need to be able to look at
但您确实需要能够看
what it's doing figure out if practice a
它在做什么，如果练习
performance impact you need to look at
您需要查看的性能影响
it and see if actually this does help
看看是否真的有帮助
you in terms of readability or it
在可读性方面
doesn't and some of those examples that
没有，其中一些例子
we showed they the refactoring was
我们向他们展示了重构
really indicating that perhaps is a
真的表明也许是
bigger design issue to address before we
在我们面前解决更大的设计问题
do these low-level refactoring so all of
做这些底层的重构，所以所有的
the reference material is available at
参考资料可在以下网址获得
this link here there's a lot more
这个链接还有很多
information about Java 8 there's a link
有关Java 8的信息，有一个链接
to there'll be a link to this video on
到此视频的链接
there there's links to slides there's
那里有幻灯片的链接
links to the code is basically all the
链接到代码基本上是所有
resources for this talk are available
此演讲的资源可用
here and now is a good time to stop and
现在是停止的好时机，
take any questions that haven't been
回答所有未曾提出的问题
answered yet ok thank you for
回答还可以，谢谢
presentation and not to include
介绍，不包括
questions we have I see a question why
我有一个问题，我看到一个问题，为什么
would an anonymous inner class be any
匿名内部类会是任何
different performance wise to Rwanda are
与卢旺达不同的表现是
they not equal ones compelled and right
他们不平等的被迫和正确
well the short answer is no they're not
好吧，简短的答案是不，他们不是
it does look like lambda expressions are
它确实看起来像lambda表达式
syntactic sugar over anonymous inner
匿名内部语法糖
types but they're not they're actually
类型，但实际上不是
different under the covers and look for
不同的掩护下寻找
Bryan gets into presentations because he
布莱恩参加演讲，因为他
does like whole hour on why they're not
喜欢整整一个小时，为什么他们不
the same thing Oracle works really hard
甲骨文真的很努力
to make sure that lambda expressions are
确保lambda表达式是
not worse performers than anonymous
表现不比匿名者差
inner types but under the covers they
内在类型，但在幕后
are not the same thing because basically
是不一样的，因为基本上
a lambda expression is not a full class
Lambda表达式不是完整的类
an anonymous inner type is a full class
匿名内部类型是完整类
with like headers and memory allocation
具有相似的标题和内存分配
and it you know it's a full-blown object
而且你知道这是一个成熟的物体
whereas lambda expressions aren't okay
但是lambda表达式不好
the next question wait wait where do we
下一个问题等待等待我们在哪里
need to change our code why isn't it
需要更改我们的代码，为什么不是
handled by come compiler if it could be
如果可能的话，由come编译器处理
handled by JIT then we wouldn't need any
由JIT处理，那么我们就不需要任何
in factory if it could be refactored by
如果可以通过工厂重构
the ID there it could be handled by JIT
它可以由JIT处理的ID
that's a really interesting question and
这是一个非常有趣的问题，
I think probably the short version is
我想大概是短版
that when IntelliJ suggests our
当IntelliJ建议我们
refactoring to you it is not saying that
向您重构并不是说
the new code is exactly the same as the
新代码与
old code under the covers in Telugu
泰卢固文掩盖下的旧代码
suggesting and new syntax to use or
建议和要使用的新语法，或
different alternative syntax to use that
使用不同的替代语法
will achieve the same aim but under the
将达到相同的目标，但根据
covers it's not compiled down to the
涵盖了它没有被编译成
same bytecode in particular some of
相同的字节码，尤其是某些
those refactorings and the the two array
那些重构和两个数组
lon let's see if I can find it and some
lon让我们看看是否可以找到它
slides better hold them
幻灯片更好地抓住他们
yes this one and discouraged here on the
是的，这一点在此不鼓励
right it does the same thing as this
对，它与此做相同的事情
code on the left but it's not same code
左侧的代码，但不是相同的代码
but it's not there's one step missing
但这不是缺少一步
we're going straight from a map tour to
我们将直接从地图游览到
a rate so the compiled code is not the
一个比率，因此编译后的代码不是
same thing and and that's because
同样的事情，那是因为
IntelliJ gets to suggest to you the
IntelliJ可以向您建议
developer this is something I think that
开发人员这是我认为的事情
does the same thing in terms of behavior
在行为方面做同样的事情
provides the same behavior as the
提供与
original code but I need you the
原始代码，但我需要你
developer to decide whether or not this
开发人员来决定是否
is something that you you really want to
是您真正想要的东西
apply and because as you saw with some
适用，因为如您所见
of these the performance shows that
这些表现表明
these are not the same operations under
这些不是相同的操作
the covers
封面
so you need to be able to you need to be
所以你需要能够
the one to make those decisions and the
做出那些决定的人
kit probably can make decisions for some
套件可能可以为某些人做出决定
not from the examples I gave but for
不是从我给的例子中，而是为了
some things but the tip is not going to
有些事情，但提示不会
go away and say oh well I think that
走开，说好吧，我认为
this should be in a raised upstream
这应该在上游
operation because it's clearly not more
操作，因为显然不多了
efficient some of these refactoring is
高效的一些重构是
I'm suggesting are to aid as the
我建议是为了帮助
developer to read things and to give
开发人员阅读事物并给予
greater readability to the code not to
更高的代码可读性
aid the the JVM to run faster okay one
帮助JVM更快地运行，好一个
next question should we perform added
我们应该执行下一个问题吗
references instead of lambda syntax oh I
引用而不是lambda语法哦
like that question and when I first
喜欢那个问题，当我第一次
started in Java 8 I really disliked
我真的不喜欢Java 8
method references I thought this weird
方法引用我认为这很奇怪
double colon thing was kind of
双冒号的东西有点
unreadable and difficult to get my head
难以理解和难以理解
round and but I have generally over time
圆，但我通常随着时间的流逝
come to prefer method references over
比起首选方法引用
lambda expressions where IntelliJ
IntelliJ的lambda表达式
suggests that I use a method reference
建议我使用方法参考
and there's a few examples of this which
这里有一些例子
whichever site so in this example the
不论哪个网站，在此示例中
map is not so useful but let me see if I
地图不是很有用，但让我看看是否
can find an example of filter let's say
可以找到一个过滤器的例子
we have I find something with a filter
我们有一个过滤器找到了一些东西
so let's say
所以说
filter I might say what have we got
过滤器我可能会说我们得到了什么
again a key I might say Tiki is not
再说一遍我可能会说Tiki不是的钥匙
equal to null and and that's kind of
等于null并且那是
fine but IntelliJ suggests to me that I
很好，但是IntelliJ建议我
can replace this with a method reference
可以用方法参考代替
which says objects non null now in this
表示对象现在非null
case I much prefer the method reference
案例我更喜欢方法参考
because I think it says to me very
因为我觉得它对我说的非常
clearly I want you to filter for all the
显然，我要您过滤所有
non null and objects so I know that the
非null和对象，所以我知道
only object I'm getting in this map
我在这张地图上得到的唯一对象
operation are not null whereas in the
操作不为null，而在
previous version I have to literally it
以前的版本我必须从字面上看
doesn't take very long but I have to
不需要很长时间，但我必须
reason around what this means
这意味着什么的原因
like not equal to null or equal to null
就像不等于null或等于null
that means not equal to ones are are
这意味着不等于是
giving go through when I'm not going
当我不走时给予通过
through and there's another example
通过，还有另一个例子
where I really like this as well which
我真的很喜欢这个
is let me see if I can kind of do sorted
让我看看我是否可以排序
comparators dot comparing and then I can
比较器点比较，然后我可以
do something like whoops well if we got
如果有的话，做得很好
on T key I get ID well that's not a
在T键上，我很好地获得了ID
great example because I just pull it out
很好的例子，因为我只是把它拔出来
out of year but with comparators up
一年过时，但比较器最多
comparing you can use a method reference
比较可以使用方法参考
to say this is the method I want you to
说这是我要你的方法
compare on so instead of having to do
比较，而不是必须做
comparing like oh one get ID - oh to get
比较就像哦，获得ID-哦获得
ID or was it Oh two - oh one I'm not
ID还是哦，两个-哦，一个我不是
really sure the comparing with the
真的确定与
method reference to me makes it really
对我的方法引用确实使
clear that this is what I want to
清楚这就是我想要的
compare I'm comparing them on ID and
比较我正在比较它们的ID和
also I can do reversed which says okay
我也可以做相反的事情
well then I can really easily sort these
好吧，我真的可以很容易地对这些进行排序
centres or thought descending or thought
中心或思想下降或思想
ascending and so that's some of the
上升，所以这是一些
places where I really like method
我真正喜欢方法的地方
references I personally prefer method
我个人更喜欢引用的方法
references Overlander expressions
参考Overlander表达式
most of the time but basically it's
大多数时候，但基本上是
going to be whatever seems to be the
将成为似乎是什么
most readable for you what
对您最可读的内容
thank and neck crushing can you provide
谢谢，脖子压伤你能提供
more details on the benefits of moving
有关搬迁好处的更多详细信息
to Java 8 result performance and
Java 8结果性能和
refactorings so I'm going to assume from
重构，所以我将假设
that question it's like if you're if
这个问题就像你是否
you've got an existing code base and
您已有一个现有的代码库，并且
you're going to run you're going to run
你要跑了你要跑了
it on Java 8 without making any changes
在Java 8上无需进行任何更改
so without applying the lambda
所以不用拉姆达
expressions without applying without
表达式不适用不
using the streams API
使用流API
so basically Java 6 code running on a
所以基本上Java 6代码在
Java 8 compiler and VM that's well shim
很好的Java 8编译器和VM
now the the benefits that I showed let's
现在我展示的好处让我们
go back to beginning or lower back yes
回到起点或后退是
here we go those like the third slide
这里我们去像第三张幻灯片
and so a lot of these changes that
这些变化很多
performance improvements in common data
通用数据的性能改进
structures changes to support
结构变化以支持
concurrency a bunch of these things and
并发这些东西
again there's links to more information
再次有更多信息的链接
from the page that links to they these
从链接到他们的页面
speed improvement in particular and you
尤其是提高速度
get those without having to do anything
不用做任何事情就能得到那些
particularly because things like hash
特别是因为像哈希这样的东西
map performs better so presumably you're
地图的效果更好，大概是
already using hash map inside your Java
已经在Java中使用哈希映射
6 style code and moving to Java 8 hash
6种样式代码并转移到Java 8哈希
map would perform generally perform
地图将执行一般
faster without you having to do anything
无需做任何事情就能更快
ok next question how will you approach a
好的下一个问题，您将如何处理
situation where you need to iterate over
您需要迭代的情况
a string multiple times to perform
一个字符串多次执行
different operations on it collect to it
对其执行不同的操作
to your collection first and then
首先到您的收藏
perform their processing or is there a
执行他们的处理还是有
better approach um I'm not sure I would
更好的方法，我不确定我会
like to see the actual code example but
喜欢看实际的代码示例，但是
I think that some of these research
我认为其中一些研究
things that we saw here some of them are
我们在这里看到的一些东西是
a bit magic and you just kind of get
有点魔术，你只是有点
three steps in one it just does it all
三个步骤合而为一
for you
为了你
and I think that as you're getting to
我认为随着您的发展
grips with some of the Java 8 features
掌握了Java 8的某些功能
it's it's important to do things
做事情很重要
incremental II so if I if I was thinking
增量II，所以如果我在想的话
in terms of a collection or some objects
在集合或某些对象方面
requiring multiple operations to be
需要多个操作
performed upon it I might write that in
执行它，我可能会写在
the code as let's say three separate
假设三个独立的代码
operations and then I'd have a test to
操作，然后我将进行测试
make sure that's working and then I
确保它正常工作，然后我
might see if I can we factor it into
可能会看看我是否可以将其纳入
either a single stream operation or yeah
是单流操作还是
I'd see if I could research it into a
我会看看是否可以将其研究为
single stream operation you should be
单流操作，您应该
able to reason around which things are
能够推理出周围的事物
inhibiting that so if I look at some of
禁止这样做，所以如果我看一些
my examples like this example I know
我的例子就像这个例子
that there's another for loop here so I
在这里还有另一个for循环，所以我
feel like this should be able to be
感觉应该这样
refracted into a single stream operation
折射为单流操作
but I know that the way that this is
但我知道这是
structured right now I can't do that
现在结构化，我不能那样做
because it's this if this map field
因为这是这个地图字段
which I need access to here and here
我需要访问这里和这里
which stops me from inlining this for
这使我无法对此进行内联
loop and similarly I have to a for each
循环，类似地，我必须每个
instead of doing something more Streamy
而不是做些流线型
because I'm passing in this set so the
因为我要传递这组，所以
problem with this particular method is
这种特定方法的问题是
and I have a number of collections that
我有很多收藏
I'm doing stuff over so I've got this
我正在做东西，所以我已经有了
found name thing and I've got this set
找到名字的东西，我有这套
here I've got this mapped field thing
这里我有这个映射的领域的东西
which also has lists inside it so I've
其中也有列表，所以我已经
got a number of different collections
有很多不同的收藏
that are interacting with each other so
彼此相互作用，所以
I'm having to iterate over all of them
我必须遍历所有这些
and in this case I know that in order to
在这种情况下，我知道为了
perform that as a single stream
作为一个流执行
operation I need to get rid of some of
操作我需要摆脱一些
those collections or collapse them in
这些集合或将其折叠
together so it would the answer is of
在一起，所以答案是
course it depends that I'd be tempted on
当然，这取决于我是否会受到诱惑
the first pass to write stuff out as a
第一次把东西写成
series of individual operations and then
一系列的个人操作，然后
see if I can figure out which of those
看看我能不能找出那些
will collapse down into into a single
会崩溃成一个单一的
operation
运作
okay good sir again a question about
好的，先生，我再问一个问题
comparing methods reference tool and
比较方法参考工具和
expressions with now performance watch
现在观看性能的表情
oh um I don't well
哦，我不好
I think they're the same I don't know I
我想他们是一样的，我不知道我
think there is some I think there's some
认为有一些我认为有一些
literature from Oracle on that but I
来自Oracle的文献，但我
think that they perform the same I don't
认为他们的表现与我不一样
know I shouldn't say anything because I
知道我不应该说什么，因为我
don't I did look it up once I can't
难道我没有查过吗
remember okay so there were a couple of
记得好吧，所以有几个
questions about their performance issues
有关其绩效问题的问题
mentioned question first question is is
提到的问题第一个问题是
there lower performance is attributed to
较低的性能归因于
erase that streams only how about
只擦除流
collection not stream right so the worst
收集不正确，所以最坏的情况
performance results that we had were
我们获得的绩效结果是
definitely around a raised up stream I'm
绝对是在高潮中
just going to try and see if I can find
只是尝试去看看我是否能找到
some of these examples and now so I find
这些例子中的一些，现在我发现
the word fun
有趣一词
one of the worst examples this is where
最糟糕的例子之一是
we're using a raised upstream and
我们在上游使用凸起的
regardless of whether we were going
不管我们是否要去
parallel or not we just couldn't get
平行与否，我们只是无法得到
performance which got anywhere near the
性能接近
original array and in this case I
原始数组，在这种情况下，我
believe that because iterating over
相信，因为迭代
arrayed like I said is very very
像我说的那样排列得非常非常
efficient and it's very difficult to to
高效，这很难
match that performance but there are
匹配的表现，但有
other cases as you're pointing out where
您指出的其他情况
that's no waste upstream as well so this
上游也没有浪费，所以这
is a map and a collect and it's not
是地图和收藏，不是
using a raised upstream this is
使用凸起的上游，这是
collection upstream and it still is not
上游收集，仍然不是
as good performance wise to look at the
作为良好的性能明智的看
code here we go it's just Keys dot
代码在这里，我们只是键点
stream and so the using streams does
流，因此使用流确实
have an impact in terms of object
对对象有影响
creation it does have an impact in terms
创造确实会产生影响
of performance so it's not it's not just
性能的问题，不是，不仅仅是
if there is no free lunch of course so
如果没有免费的午餐当然
yes there is a cost to using streams and
是的，使用流会产生成本，并且
directly not just arrays streams but the
直接不仅是数组流，而且
arrays dot stream is particularly bad
数组点流特别糟糕
which is why I call that out okay and
这就是为什么我称其为好，
another question rather this is all
另一个问题，这就是全部
these performance issue is possible to
这些性能问题可能
be solved in future versions of Java or
在将来的Java版本中解决，或者
x9 okay yes so the performance of Java 8
x9好的，是的，所以Java 8的性能
has been getting better even even just
甚至已经变得越来越好
Java 8 so you know you get all these
Java 8，所以您知道所有这些
different updates for the job 8 the
作业8的不同更新
non-running release 112 whatever that
非运行版本112
means
手段
so even without having to go to Java 9
因此，即使不必使用Java 9
we're getting improved performance under
我们正在改善性能
the covers for getting improved
改进的盖子
performance with things like lambda
Lambda之类的性能
expressions and so forth these streams
表达式等等这些流
API one of the nice things about the
API的好处之一
streams API is because how its
流API是因为它的
implemented is hidden away from you and
实施隐藏在你身边
you just interact with what you want to
你只是与你想要的互动
achieve they can continue to iterate
实现他们可以继续迭代
over improving the performance for
过度提高性能
streams API without impacting you using
流API，而不会影响您使用
the streams API they can do that under
流API，他们可以在
the colors so that's definitely going on
颜色，所以肯定会继续
there's all sorts of other stuff coming
还有各种各样的其他东西
into Java 9 and Java 10 which will
进入Java 9和Java 10
improve the performance - one of the
提高性能-其中之一
things I do want to emphasize though is
我想强调的是
that even in a case like this where it
即使在这样的情况下
looks like this refactored code is
看起来这个重构的代码是
really horror
真的很恐怖
performance compared to the original
与原始性能相比
code I did say it earlier but it's worth
我之前说过的代码，但值得
reiterating micro benchmarks like this
重申像这样的微观基准
don't necessarily mean that your
不一定代表您
application is going to perform slower
应用程序的执行速度会变慢
if you do this refactoring because in
如果您执行此重构，因为
the grand scheme of things your
事物的宏伟计划
application does a lot of other things
应用程序还有很多其他功能
it talks to other services and network
它与其他服务和网络对话
cords are expensive you know it talks to
电线很贵，你知道它会说话
databases it has to respond to the user
它必须响应用户的数据库
there's all sorts of other stuff
还有各种各样的其他东西
happening as lots of interactions
发生大量互动
between things so the fact that these
事情之间的事实，这些
three lines of code or whatever don't
三行代码或其他代码
perform quite as fast as the original
表现与原版一样快
lines of code may not have any impact on
几行代码可能不会对
the overall performance of your
您的整体表现
application as well and you might find
应用程序，您可能会发现
that some of the improvements around
周围的一些改进
things like garbage collections and the
诸如垃圾收集之类的东西
improvements around the disputer some of
围绕争议者的改进
the collections that you're using
您正在使用的收藏集
they might offset some of these these
他们可能会抵消其中的一些
performance tests which show that the
性能测试表明
performance isn't quite as good so you
性能不是很好，所以你
need to measure stuff in the overall
需要整体衡量
scope of your whole application not just
您整个应用程序的范围而不仅仅是
these micro benchmarks okay one more
这些微型基准还可以
question what about performance of
质疑如何表现
Flanders and any miss pross's island is
法兰德斯和普罗斯小姐的孤岛是
bad or good for performance or it
对性能不好或好
depends on how we implement them it
取决于我们如何实施它们
seems like it's all about readable code
似乎都是关于可读代码的
versus better performance it does feel a
与更好的性能相比，确实感觉
bit like that the I would say that the
有点像我会说
world so my example is the lambda of
世界，所以我的例子是
using the lambda expressions let's go
使用lambda表达式开始
back my lambda expressions performed
返回我执行的lambda表达式
better so in a whole bunch of cases in
更好，所以在很多情况下
this report here there's a whole bunch
这个报告这里有一大堆
of cases where the lambda expressions
lambda表达式的情况
perform better than the anonymous types
比匿名类型表现更好
so you get increased readability and
这样您可以提高可读性，
better performance I actually had to
我实际上不得不改善性能
search through this document to find one
搜索此文档以找到一个
example where the lambda expression
lambda表达式的示例
didn't perform quite as well as one of
表现不如以下之一
the anonymous inner types so for lambda
匿名内部类型，所以对于lambda
expressions in particular they are an
特别是它们是一个
Oracle which really hard to make sure
甲骨文真的很难确保
that they were no worse in performance
他们的表现并不差
than anonymous types and they're often
比匿名类型更常见
better and as I said the performance of
更好，正如我所说的
these is getting better as well because
这些也越来越好，因为
of optimizations to the JVM itself yeah
对JVM本身的优化是的
thanks
谢谢
um when question hint results or
嗯，当问题提示出现时，或
parallel are calculated in isolation
并行计算
would it make a difference if we do do
如果我们这样做会有所作为吗
parallel in collection of app I guess
我猜应用程序中的并行
then with parallel I might begin
然后平行我可能会开始
consuming or using threads that could
消耗或使用可能
have been used for other operations I'm
已经用于其他操作
not sure if that is what can I notice I
不知道那是什么我能注意到我
quite understand because if the question
很明白，因为如果问题
is running parallel in production
在生产中并行运行
different to running parallel in these
与这些并行运行不同
tests as I understood the question it is
根据我的理解测试
let's say we we use parallel so we need
假设我们使用并行，因此我们需要
to use leverage other threads and so we
利用其他线程，所以我们
wonder if we affect the performance of
想知道我们是否会影响
the application by doing that
通过这样做的应用程序
considering we consumed the thread which
考虑到我们消耗了线程
could be used for a bit operation I I
可用于位操作II
don't think it works that way maybe I'm
不要以为这样就行了
misunderstanding the question but what
误解了问题，但是什么
what parallel is doing is under covers
并行在做什么
it uses the fork/join framework so it
它使用fork / join框架，因此
will be spinning up if you like its own
如果您喜欢它自己，它将旋转
threads and running the whole point of
线程并运行整个过程
that parallel is to run the work on
该并行是要继续进行工作
individual CPUs or cause and a few
单个CPU或原因以及一些
physical CPUs so for example on my
物理CPU，例如
macbook I can get parallel to use four
Macbook我可以并行使用四个
cores nice and easily and just basically
核心很容易，而且基本上
make the most out the hardware that's
充分利用硬件
the point about parallel to make the
关于平行点
most of the hardware now of course if
当然，现在大多数硬件
you've got parallel threads making the
你有并行线程使
most of all of the CPUs it could be
大多数的CPU可能是
pushing other threads off the CPU so
将其他线程推离CPU，这样
they don't get any time I don't really
他们没有时间我不是真的
know how to scheduling work underneath
知道如何安排下面的工作
the covers but you're not going to be
封面，但你不会
it's not going to be interfering with
它不会干扰
data on other thread so it's not going
其他线程上的数据，所以它不会
to be reusing other threads and
重用其他线程
interfering with them from a data point
从数据点干扰他们
of view it might be feeling the CPU away
看来可能感觉CPU不在了
from them but I don't believe there's
从他们那里，但我不相信
gonna you don't have to worry about
你不必担心
things like a about thread safety in the
关于线程安全的事情
way that we traditionally had to yeah I
传统上我们不得不接受的方式
think you are right here and and okay
认为你就在这里，还可以
let's move closer oh there's a lot
让我们靠近一点哦，还有很多
question do does IntelliJ IDEA provide
IntelliJ IDEA提供的问题吗
suggestions to refactor from near the
从附近重构的建议
time to ja a time API so I could try to
时间到一个时间API，所以我可以尝试
answer the question enjoy Delia doesn't
回答问题，享受Delia不会
suggest it yet there is an issue in
建议它，但是有一个问题
issue tracker and we still track roads
问题跟踪器，我们仍然跟踪道路
and feel free to go through it and
并随时通过它
definitely we can implement that yeah I
绝对可以实现，是的，我
really wanted to show you some day some
真的想有一天给你看
time stuff because I really like the new
时间的东西，因为我真的很喜欢新
date and time and API but I don't have
日期和时间以及API，但我没有
any really good examples I did see that
我确实看到的任何非常好的例子
there's the use of the obsolete
有过时的使用
obsolete date/time API but that's not
过时的日期/时间API，但这不是
the other time that's the java.util date
另一个时间是java.util日期
and Java util calendar yes I think that
和Java util日历，是的，我认为
all without the normal questions in case
一切都没有正常的问题
you have other questions feel free to
您还有其他疑问
ask them in Twitter or implement we'll
在Twitter上询问他们或实施我们
be publishing the recording soon and if
即将发布录音，如果
you'll find some question not addressed
您会发现一些未解决的问题
please share it with us actually you can
请实际上与我们分享
always contact me over Twitter
总是通过Twitter与我联系
cool so thank you for your time hexa I
太酷了，谢谢您为我度过的时光
thank you bye
谢谢你，再见